it is time to play on my way to steal
your girl gift
Edition by now you may have come across
one of the internet's finest memes on my
way to steal your girl where people post
gifts and photos and then with Casanova
confidence hashtag it on my way to steal
your girl for example this Sharp
Shooting segue Slayer
bam all my way to see your girl and if
that fails on my way to teach children's
karate lessons way too seriously
so comedians I'm going to show you some
sweet gifts we found searching on on my
way to steal your girl for 250 points
I'm going you to tell me another thing
they're on their way to do all right
this Wiggly
wandy
what crystalia on the way to dry my
[Laughter]
I
mean I would hope it'd be dry by the
time she gets to he yeah yeah yeah you
know Edwards on my way to being a human
vagina Roomba
Point wait a
minute hang on a second isn't that just
the
WBA yes very good man very good next one
how about this paddling
[Applause]
[Music]
tug Mr DEA on my way to drown your son
[Applause]
why
you you could definitely see that
happening if you I mean like if just
playful though and the kid's
like and then yeah why did it have to
get too real yeah because I used to be
allowed up on the couch before you
arrived yeah so cute next up this
squatting
stallion
crystalia on my way to raise awareness
about the dangers of
[Laughter]
polio wheny coming on my way to eat out
Bruno Mars
F
yep I you don't think I could do that I
could do that you can do that do it do
it do it do it
it
oh
whoops hey guys guys guys guys guys guys
guys guys full disclosure I can't do
that I don't know what is it that he's
doing though just is he he's just
doing like just and just
bleeding Chris it's really harder than
it looks Chris if you die like four
shows won't have a host
please true all right next one this
goofy dude huh what about
[Applause]
this by the way on my way to Whitney's
house cuz she's into it
[Applause]
yeah I'm not mad at that I'm I'm a
shower not a
grower
uh on my way back from stealing your
girl
[Applause]
yeah